Jenny Dinh

5483 Danbury Circle, Lake in the Hills, IL, 60156 (224) 622-7111 • jenny.p.dinh@gmail.com • www.github.com/jdinh3 www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-dinh • https://jdinh3.github.io/react-portfolio/work

Summary:

A full-stack web developer with several years of work experience in Audio Engineering and Sales management who is eager to learning new technical skills and methods. Leveraged strong teamwork ethic and problem-solving skills to successfully create Full Stack applications in an agile environment. Enjoys using creativity and contributing new ideas to team environments.

Education:

Georgia Institute of Technology • Full Stack Web Development Certificate

A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills for Full Stack Web Development using Javascript. • Completion: June 2021

Columbia College Chicago • Chicago, IL • Graduation: May 2017 • Cumulative GPA: 3.8/4.0

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Audio Engineering • Minor: Management

Huntley High School • Huntley, IL • Graduation: June 2013

Technical Skills:

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React JS, JQuery, Node JS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, Bootstrap, JQuery, APIs, Node JS, Insomnia, Git, and GitHub

Projects:

Employee Directory

Deployed Site: https://jdinh3.github.io/employee-directory/ • GitHub Repository: https://github.com/jdinh3/employee-directory

- A searchable and sortable directory of employees.
- Technologies used: React JS, Random User API, Bootstrap

Fitness Tracker

Deployed Site: https://stark-refuge-78989.herokuapp.com/?id=6096d3b98d88890015c4f1a4

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/jdinh3/fitness-tracker

- A web application designed for users to document and track their workouts
- Technologies used: MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Bootstrap

Work Experience:

Aerotek

Engineering Recruiter • Schaumburg, IL • October 2020 – March 2021

- Identified qualified candidates through various recruiting and sourcing tools
- Screened and interviewed qualified candidates for different engineering roles

PSAV

Sales Manager • Loews Vanderbilt Hotel • June 2019 - March 2020

- Consulted clients on audio visual needs for their conferences.
- Built rapport and maintained healthy customer relationships.

Sales Coordinator • Gaylord Opryland Resort • June 2018 – June 2019

AV Technician • Loews Chicago Hotel • November 2016 – June 2018

- Set up audio, video and lighting equipment according to clients' needs
- Troubleshooted and fixed technical problems on-site.